Okay guys, here we go, here we go, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3
Thank you.
Hey!
I'll be right with you.
So, Cameron, here you go.
Nine schools in ten years.
My, my. Army brat?
Yeah, my dad is, uh...
That's enough.
I'm sure you won't find Padua any different than your old schools.
Same little asswipe. Shit for brains everywhere.
Excuse me?
Did you just say...
Am I in the right office?
Not anymore, you're not.
I've got deviants to see and a novel to finish.
Now scoot.
Scoot! Okay.
Thanks.
Patrick Verona.
I see we're making our visits a weekly ritual.
Only so we can have these moments together.
Should I, uh, hit the lights?
Oh, very clever, kangaroo boy.
It says here you exposed yourself in the cafeteria.
I was joking with the lunch lady.
It was a bratwurst.
Bratwurst?
Aren't we the optimist?
Next time, keep it in your pouch.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hello. Michael Ekman. I'm supposed to show you around.
Oh, hi. Thank God.
You know, normally they send down one of those audio-visual geeks.
No, I do. I know what you mean.
Hey, Michael, where should I put the slides?
Michael.
So, uh, Cameron, here's the breakdown.
Over there, we've got your basic beautiful people.
Now, listen, unless they talk to you first, don't bother.
Wait, is that your rule or theirs?
Watch. Hey, there.
Eat me.
You see that?
To the left, we have the coffee kids.
That was Costa Rican, butthead.
Very edgy. Don't make any sudden movements around me.
These delusionals are your white rastas.
They're big Marley fans. They think they're black.
Semi-political, but mostly...
Smoke a lot of weed?
Yeah. These guys...
Wait, wait. Let me guess. Cowboys?
Yeah, but the closest they've come to a cow is McDonald's.
Here it comes!
McDonald's.
These are your future MBAs.
We're all Ivy League accepted.
Yuppie Greed is back, my friend.
Hey, guys. How you doing?
Close it, Bogey.
Yesterday, I was their god.
What happened?
Bogey Lowenstein started a rumor that I...
that I buy my eyes off at an outlet mall.
So they kicked you out?
This will take over, but don't worry. He'll pay.
Now, over here...
Oh, my God.
What group is she in?
You don't even think about it, group.
Bianca Stratford. She's a soft...
I burn, I pine, I perish.
Of course you do.
You know, she's beautiful and deep, I'm sure.
Yeah, but see, there's a difference between like and love.
Because I like my Skechers, but I love my Prada backpack.
But I love my Skechers.
That's because you don't have a Prada backpack.
Oh.
Listen, forget her incredibly uptight father,
and it's a widely known fact that the Stratford sisters
aren't allowed to date.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Whatever.
Hey.
You up in the same old thing, huh?
Okay, then. What did everyone think of The Sun Also Rises?
I loved it. He's so romantic.
Romantic? Hemingway?
He was an abusive alcoholic misogynist
who squandered half his life hanging around Picasso
trying to nail his leftovers.
As opposed to a bitter, self-righteous hag
who has no friends?
Pipe down, Chachi!
I guess in this society, being male and an asshole
makes you worthy of our time.
What about Sylvia Plath or Charlotte Bronte or Simone de Beauvoir?
What did I miss?
The oppressive patriarchal values that dictate our education.
Good.
Hey, hey!
Mr. Morgan, is there any chance we could get Kat to take her mito before she comes to class?
Someday you're gonna get bitch slapped, and I'm not gonna do a thing to stop it.
And Kat, I want to thank you for your point of view.
I know how difficult it must be for you to overcome
all those years of upper middle class suburban oppression.
Must be tough.
But the next time you storm the PTA,
crusading for better lunch meat or whatever it is you
white girls complain about, ask them why they can't buy
a book written by a black man.
That's right, Mom.
Don't even get me started on you two.
No problem.
Anything else?
Yeah, go to the office.
You're pissing me off.
What? Mr. Morgan.
Later.
What?
Undulating with desire,
Adrian removes her red...
Crimson cape
at the sight of Reginald Stiff and...
Judith!
What's another word for engorged?
I'll look it up.
Okay.
Swollen.
Turgid.
Tumescent.
Perfect.
So, I hear you were terrorizing Mr. Morgan's class again.
Expressing my opinion is not a terrorist action.
The way you expressed your opinion to Bobby Ridgway?
By the way, his testicle retrieval operation went quite well,
in case you're interested.
I still maintain that he kicked himself in the balls.
The point is, Kat...
Kat!
People perceive you as somewhat...
Tempestuous?
Heinous bitch is the term used most often.
You might want to work on that.
Thank you.
As always, thank you for your excellent guidance.
I'll let you get back to Reginald's quivering member.
Quivering member.
I like that.
Virgin alert. Favorite.
Looking good, ladies.
Oh, she's out of reach, even for you.
No one's out of reach for me.
You want to put money on that?
Money I've got.
This I'm going to do for fun.
Who's that guy?
It's Joey Donner.
He's a jerk off and a model.
He's a model?
A model.
Mostly regional stuff, but he's rumored to have
a big tube sock out coming out.
Really?
Really.
Man, look at her.
Is she always so...
Rapid?
How can you say that? She's totally...
Conceded.
What are you talking about?
There's more to her than you think.
I mean, look at the way she smiles,
and look at her eyes, man.
She's totally pure.
You're missing what's there.
No, Cameron, no.
What's there is a snotty little princess
wearing a strategically planned sundress
to make guys like us realize that we can never touch her.
And guys like Joey realize that they want to.
She, my friend, is what we will spend the rest of our lives not having.
Put her in your spank bank, move on.
No.
Move on.
No, you're wrong about her.
I mean, you know, not about the spanking part, but the rest.
You're wrong.
I'm wrong?
You want to take a shot?
Be my guest.
She's actually looking for a French tutor.
Are you serious?
That's perfect.
Do you speak French?
Well, no, but I will.
Hey!
Your little Rambo look is out, Kat.
Didn't you read last month's Cosmo?
Run along.
I know you can be overwhelmed, and you can be underwhelmed,
but can you ever just be whelmed?
I think you can in Europe.
Hi, ladies.
You, uh, sweet young things like a wrap?
Careful on the leather.
That's a charming new development.
It's disgusting.
Remove head from sphincter, then drive.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Just a minor encounter with the shrew.
It's your girlfriend's sister
Wait, that's Bianca's sister?
The mewling, rampalian wretch herself
Stay cool, bro
Yeah, see you later
Look out!
My balls!
Oh, boy
Oh, oh, oh
Oh
Oh!
Ooh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yeah! Woo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha!
Sunshine on the window
Makes me happy like I should be
Outside, all around me
It's really sleazy, but it hits me
Don't tell me you can't see
What it means to me
Hello, Katarina. Make anyone cry today?
Sadly, no. But it's only 4.30.
Hi, Daddy. Hello, precious.
And where have you been? Nowhere.
What's this? It says Sarah Lawrence.
I got in! I got in!
Uh, honey, that's great,
but isn't Sarah Lawrence on the other side of the country?
the other side of the country?
That's the basis of its appeal.
I thought we decided you were going to stay here
and go to school.
You dub, like me, be a husky.
No, you decided.
Oh, OK, so what, you just pick up and leave, is that it?
Let's hope so.
Ask Bianca who drove her home.
Cat, don't change the drove.
Who drove you home?
Now, don't get upset, Daddy, but there's this boy.
Who's a flaming imbecile.
Please.
And I think he might ask me.
Please, I think I know what he's going to ask you.
And I think I know the answer.
No, it's always no.
What are the two house rules?
Number one, no dating till you graduate.
Number two, no dating till you graduate.
That's it.
Daddy, that's so unfair.
All right, you want to know what's unfair?
This is for you two.
This morning, I delivered a set of twins to a 15-year-old girl.
Do you know what she said to me?
I'm a crack whore who should have made my skeezy boyfriend wear a condom?
Close.
But no.
She said I should have listened to my father.
She did not.
Well, that's what she would have said if she wasn't so doped up.
Can we focus on me for a second, please?
I am the only girl in school who's not dating.
Oh, no, you're not. Your sister doesn't date.
And I don't intend to.
And why is that again?
Have you seen the unwatched miscreants that go to that school?
Where did you come from? Planet Loser?
As opposed to Planet... Look at me. Look at me.
Okay, here's how we solve this one.
Old rule out. New rule.
Bianca can date.
When she does.
But she's a mutant. What if she never dates?
Then you'll never date. Oh, I like that.
And I'll get to sleep at night.
The deep slumber of a father whose daughters aren't out being impregnated.
We'll talk about Sarah Lawrence later.
Fine.
Wait, Daddy!
I gotta go.
Can't you just find some blind deaf retard to take you to the movies so I can have one date?
I'm sorry, looks like you'll just have to miss out on the witty repartee of Joey Eat Me Donner.
You suck.
You suck?
Hi.
Coming up this quick, Roxanne, Corinne, and Andrew Jarrett
are having an incredibly horrendous public breakup on the quad.
Again.
Oh, yeah, um, okay, I thought that we'd, um,
start with pronunciation, if that's all right with you.
Not the hacking and gagging and spitting part, please.
Well, uh, there is an alternative.
There is?
Yeah, uh, French food.
We could, uh, eat some together, uh...
Saturday night.
You're asking me out?
That's so cute!
What's your name again?
Cameron.
Listen, I know that your dad doesn't let you date,
but I thought that if it was for French class that...
Oh, wait a minute.
Curtis...
Cameron.
My dad just came up with a new rule. I can date when my sister does.
You're kidding. Let me ask you, do you like sailing?
Because I read about this place that rents out boats.
A beaucoup problemo, Calvin, in case you haven't heard.
My sister's a particularly hideous breed of loser.
Yeah, yeah, I noticed she's a little, um, antisocial. Why is that?
Unsolved mystery. She used to be really popular,
and then it was like she got sick of it or something.
Theories abound as to why, but I'm pretty sure she's just incapable of human interaction.
Plus, she's a bitch.
Well, yeah, but I'm sure, you know, that there are lots of guys who wouldn't mind going out with a difficult woman.
I mean, you know, people jump out of airplanes and ski off cliffs. It'd be like extreme dating, huh?
You think you could find someone that extreme?
Yeah, sure, why not?
And you'd do that for me?
Hell yes!
I mean, you know, I could look into it.
Now, I have gathered a group of guys.
Couldn't be more perfect. Padua's finest.
Hi. How you doing?
Would any of you be interested in dating Katerina Stratford?
Oh, I've never been that ripped.
Maybe if we were the last two people alive and there were no sheep.
Are there sheep?
Ah!
Did I or did I not tell you it was pointless?
No one will go out with her.
Hey, what about him?
Him? No, don't look at him, okay?
He's a criminal.
I heard he lit a state trooper on fire.
He just did a year in San Quentin.
Yeah, well, then at least he's horny.
I'm serious, man. He's whacked.
He sold his own liver on the black market
for a new set of speakers.
He's our guy.
Hi.
How you doing?
Listen.
Hi.
Okay.
Later then.
How do we get him to date Kat?
I don't know.
I mean, uh, we could pay him.
But we don't have any money.
Yeah, well, what we need is a backer.
What's that?
Someone with money who's stupid.
Oh, yeah.
Is that a peach fruit roll up?
Because you don't see many.
Oh, oh, OK.
Yeah, all right.
Are you lost?
No, actually, I just came by to chat.
We don't chat.
Well, actually, I thought that I'd run an idea by you,
just to see if you're interested.
I'm not.
Well, hear me out.
Now, you want Bianca, right?
But, uh, she can't go out with you
because her sister is this insane head case,
and no one will go out with her, right?
Does this conversation have a purpose?
What I think you need to do is you
need to hire a guy who will go out with her, someone who
doesn't scare so easily.
That guy?
I heard he ate a live duck once.
Everything but the beak and feet.
Clearly, he's a solid investment.
What's in it for you?
Hey, I'm walking down the hall and I say hello to you.
You say hello to me.
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
You're cool by association.
I'll think about it.
We're done now.
Yeah.
What are you doing getting him involved?
Relax now. Relax.
We let him pretend he's calling the shots.
While he's busy setting things up, you have time to be on it.
That is a good idea.
All right.
I have a dick on my face, don't I?
Now remember, guys.
Rip it.
And rip it.
Hey, how you doing?
I had some great duck last night.
Do I know you?
You see that girl?
Yeah.
That's Kat Stratford.
I want you to go out with her.
Yeah, sure, Sparky.
Look, I can't take out her sister
until Kat starts dating.
You see, their dad's whacked out.
He's got this rule where the girls...
That's a touching story. It really is.
Not my problem.
Would you be willing to make it your problem
if I provide generous compensation?
You're gonna pay me to take out some chick?
Mm-hmm.
How much?
20 bucks.
Fine. 30.
Well, let's think about this.
If we go to the movies, that's, uh, 15 bucks.
We got popcorn that's 53
And she'll want raisinets, right?
So we're looking at 75 bucks
This isn't a negotiation
Take it or leave it, Trailer Park
50 bucks and we got a deal, Fabio
Great practice, everybody
Good hustle, Stratford
Thanks, Mr. Chapin
Hi.
How are you?
Come on.
Good job, man.
Good job.
Hey.
Hey there, girly.
How you doing?
Sweating like a pig, actually, and yourself.
Now, there's a way to get a guy's attention, huh?
My mission in life.
But obviously, I struck your fancy so you see it worked.
The world makes sense again.
Pick up on Friday, then.
Oh, right.
Uh-huh.
Well, tonight I'll take you places you've never been before.
Like where? The 7-Eleven on Broadway?
Do you even know my name, screw boy?
I know a lot more than you think.
Doubtful. Very doubtful.
We are screwed.
Hey, no, hey, I don't want to hear that defeatist attitude.
I want to hear you upbeat.
We are screwed.
Hey, Coach Chapin!
Run, Bogey!
Have you ever considered a new look?
I mean, seriously, you could have some definite potential buried under all this hostility.
I'm not hostile. I'm annoyed.
Why don't you try being nice? People wouldn't know what to think.
You forget I don't care what people think.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
You don't always have to be who they want you to be, you know.
I happen to like being adored, thank you.
Where'd you get the pearls?
Their mom's.
And you've been what, hiding them for three years?
No, Daddy found them in a drawer last week.
So you're just gonna start wearing them now?
It's not like she's coming back to claim them.
to claim them.
Besides, they look good on me.
Trust me, they don't.
Nice ride.
Vintage fenders.
Are you following me?
I was in the laundromat.
I saw your car.
Came over to say hi.
Hi.
Not a big talker, huh?
Depends on the topic.
My fenders don't really whip me into a verbal frenzy.
You're not afraid of me, are you?
Afraid of you?
Why would I be afraid of you?
Well, most people are.
Well, I'm not.
Well, maybe you're not afraid of me,
but I'm sure you've thought about me naked, huh?
Am I that transparent?
I want you.
I need you, oh baby, oh baby.
What is it, asshole day?
You mind?
Not at all.
You bitch!
Whoops.
Whoops?
My insurance does not cover PMS.
Well, then tell them I had a seizure.
This is about Sarah Lawrence.
Are you punishing me because I want you to stay close to home?
Aren't you punishing me because mom left?
You think you could leave her out of this?
Fine, then stop making my decisions for me.
I'm your father.
That's my right.
So what I want doesn't matter.
You're 18. You don't know what you want.
And you won't know what you want till you're 45.
And even if you get it, you'll be too old to use it.
I want to go to an East Coast school.
I want you to trust me to make my own choices.
And I want you to stop trying to control my life just
because you can't control yours.
Oh, yeah.
What I want.
We'll continue this later.
Can't wait.
Did you just maim Joey's car?
Yeah, looks like you're going to have to take the bus.
Has the fact that you're completely psycho
managed to escape your attention?
Dying!
When I shell out 50, I expect results.
Yeah, I'm on it.
Watching that bitch violate my car doesn't count as a date.
Now, if you don't get any, I don't get any.
So get some.
I just thought my price.
What?
$100 a date in advance.
Forget it.
Well, forget her sister then.
You better hope you're smooth as you think you are, Verona.
Go.
Oh, you go.
I went before.
We know what you're trying to do with Cat Stratford.
Is that right?
And what do you plan to do about it?
Help you out.
Why's that?
The situation is, my man Cameron here
has a major Jones for Bianca Stratford.
What is it with this chick?
She have beer-flavored nipples?
Hey.
I think I speak correctly
when I say that Cameron's love is pure.
Pure than, say, Joey Donner's.
Look, I'm in on this for the cash.
Donna can plow wherever he wants.
Okay, there will be no plowing.
Patrick, uh, Pat, let me explain something to you here.
Uh, we set this whole thing up so Cameron can get the girl.
Cameron, Joey's just a pawn.
So you two are gonna help me tame the wild beast?
Absolutely.
We'll do some research.
We'll find out what she likes.
We are your guys.
And he means then a strictly non-prison movie type of one?
Uh, let's start here.
Now, Friday night, Bogey Lowenstein is having a party.
It's the perfect opportunity.
Perfect opportunity for what?
For you to take out Cat.
I'll think about it.
And for a little payback.
This is gonna be some party.
Let's do this.
Okay, now this is really important, okay?
Which one do you like better?
Um, I think I like the white shirt better.
Yeah, it's more...
Depensive?
Damn, I'm just going for thoughtful.
So, are you going to Bogey Lounge Brass thing on Friday night?
Yeah, I might.
Good, because you know, I'm not going to bother if you won't be there.
See you there?
Okay.
All right.
So, uh, have you heard about Bogey Lowenstein's party?
Yes.
and I really, really, really want to go.
But you know I can't.
Not unless my sister does.
Yeah, I know, I'm working on that.
But so far, you know, she's not going for my guy.
She's not a...
Katie Lang fan? No.
I found a picture of Jared Leto in her drawer once,
so I'm pretty sure she's not harboring same-sex tendencies.
Okay, so that's the kind of guy she likes, like pretty guys?
I don't know.
All I've ever heard her say is that she died
dating guy that smokes.
Okay, all right, no smoking. What else?
You're asking me to investigate the inner workings
of my sister's twisted mind?
I don't think so.
Well, nothing else has worked.
I mean, uh, we need to go behind enemy lines here.
Okay, here we go.
Uh, class schedule, reading list, date book,
concert tickets, concert tickets.
Aha! Black panties.
What does that tell us?
She wants to have sex someday, that's what.
She could just like the color.
You don't buy black lingerie unless you want someone to see it.
Oh.
So, uh...
Can I see your room?
No.
Oh.
A girl's room is very personal.
Oh, okay, just a second.
Nice bike.
Yeah, you think so?
Yeah.
Wow.
Is this what a bar looks like?
Don't touch anything.
You may get hepatitis.
So what do you got for me?
A little insight to a very complicated girl.
Excuse me, just one question before we start.
Should you be drinking alcohol when you don't have a liver?
What?
Nothing, nothing.
All right, first thing, Cat hates smokers.
So you're telling me I'm a non-smoker.
Yes, but just for now.
And here's another problem.
Bianca said that Kat likes pretty guys.
Are you telling me I'm not a pretty guy?
Very pretty.
Yeah, I just wasn't sure.
I didn't know.
You know.
All right, yeah, OK.
Here's this.
Likes.
Thai food, feminist prose, and angry girl music
of the indie rock Persuasion.
Here's a list of CDs that she has in her room.
So I'm supposed to buy her some noodles and a book
and sit around listening to chicks who can't
play their instruments, right?
Have you ever been to Club Skunk?
Your favorite band's playing there tomorrow night.
I can't be seen at Club Skunk, all right?
But she'll be there.
She's got tickets.
Listen, a sale to your ears for one night.
She has a pair of black underwear, if that helps.
Couldn't hurt, right?
I'm talking.
We can talk
We can talk about it
If I'm wrong
If I'm wrong I'll take your blame
We can talk
As the hours slip away
As my own
I could call another day
Come on, come on
My memories have been
Sweet, so easy
A mystery
I've got my ears
Pressed to the glass
Pressed to the wall
Spotted away
It's your second face
I didn't see
About what I heard
Verona, what are you doing here tonight?
I need a hot dog!
All the things I didn't love about you
Too hot?
If you're planning on asking me out again, you might as well just get it over with.
Do you mind? You're kind of ruining this for me.
You're not surrounded by your usual cloud of smoke.
I know. I quit. Apparently they're bad for you.
You think?
You know, these guys that know bikini kill and raincoats, they're not bad.
You know who the raincoats are.
Why, don't you?
I was watching you out there before. I've never seen you look so sexy.
Huh?
Come to Bogey's party with me.
You never give up, do you?
Was that a yes?
No.
Well, then was that a no?
I'll see you at 9.30 then.
Should have used the window.
Hi, Daddy.
Hi.
Where are we going?
Well, if you must know, a small study group of friends.
Otherwise known as an orgy?
Mr. Strafford, it's just a party.
And hell is just a sauna.
Do you know anything about a party?
People expect me to be there.
Cat's not going, you're not going.
Why can't you be normal?
Define normal.
Bogie Lowenstein's party is normal.
What's a Bogie Lowenstein?
Bogie's party is just a lame excuse
for all the idiots at our school to drink beer and rub up
against each other in hopes of distracting themselves
from the pathetic emptiness of their meaningless consumer
driven lives.
Can you, for just one night, forget that you're completely
wretched and be my sister?
Please?
Come on, Cat, please do this for me.
Fine, I'll make an appearance.
No!
It's starting.
It's just a party, Daddy.
I want you to wear the belly.
Daddy, no.
Not all night.
Just around the living room for a minute
so you can understand the full weight of your decisions.
I am perfectly aware...
Listen to me.
Every time you even think about kissing a boy,
I want you to picture wearing this under your halter top.
You are so completely unbalanced.
We're going now.
All right, wait a minute.
No drinking, no drugs, no kissing,
no tattoos, no piercings,
no ritual animal slaughters of any kind.
Oh, God, I'm giving them ideas.
Daddy!
What are you doing here?
9.30, right?
I'm early.
Whatever, I'm driving.
You knocked up your sister.
So then Bianca says that I was right,
that she didn't wear the Kenneth Coles with that dress
because she thought that, you know, it was a mixing genres, right?
And the fact that I noticed, and this is a direct quote, listen,
really meant something.
You told me that part already.
I've been thinking about it all the time.
Can you stop being so self-involved for one minute?
How do I look?
You look like my great-uncle Milton.
You think I should lose the tie?
Yeah.
Maybe you're right.
I'm just so nervous.
And I'm also very excited.
I'm nervous, I'm excited.
It's all very mixed up.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Just calm down, all right?
Shh.
Shh! The last party I went to was at Chuck E. Cheese.
You want to talk about some fun. That's a good time.
Hey-oh!
Now remember, guys, don't touch anything.
Oh!
What did I tell you?
Oh. Must be Nigel with the brie.
Oh.
Oh, yeah!
You know, I'm thinking of getting a Tercel.
Yeah, that's a Toyota.
It has dual side airbags and a spacious back seat.
Kiss me.
Kiss him.
Okay.
Good.
Hey, thanks, man.
Oh.
Sweet.
Looking fresh tonight, pussycat.
Wait, was that...
Did your hairline just recede?
Hey, where are you going?
Away.
Your sister here?
Stay away from my sister.
Oh, I'll stay away from your sister.
But I can't guarantee she'll stay away from me.
Fight!
Ooh! Fight!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Come on!
Hit him!
You guys, please, take it outside!
Thank you!
Hey, Cat, look who found me.
You found me.
Bianca, wait.
Please do not address me in public.
No, there's something I need to tell you.
Look, I am busy enjoying my adolescence,
so scamper off and do the same.
But my...
Want one?
What is this?
Right on, sister.
I've been looking all over the place for you.
I'm getting trashed, man.
Isn't that what you're supposed to do at a party?
What do you want to do?
Funny.
You're the only one.
Later.
I will win.
I feel like that.
I'm on my way.
Change the cat.
Lord of the dance.
Hi, Heather.
Bite me.
Should have kept the tie.
Hey, have you seen her around anywhere?
Relax. Relax.
I'm fine.
Follow the love.
Hi, Bianca.
Oh, hi, Cameron.
Um, you know Chastity?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I think we have art together, right?
Neat.
So, um...
You...
You really look amazing.
Thanks.
And we all know I look amazing.
Bianca, let's go. We're all congregating around Mr. Cuervo.
Um, I'll see you around, okay?
So I've got the Sears catalog thing going, and the tube sock gig.
That is gonna be huge.
And I'm up for hemorrhoid cream ad next week.
I know it sounds kind of gross, but I get to do some after work.
Oh, shit.
You see what I did there?
Uh-huh.
That was underwear.
I'll show you the bathing suit one again.
You see the difference?
I'm not going to show you the bathing suit one again.
I'm going to show you the underwear.
You see the difference?
All right, I'll show you.
Let's go.
Oh!
I'm spending time with you.
You'll never be mine.
Is it me or does this party all of a sudden suck?
Really? Really?
Thank you.
Hey. Hey, Kat, why don't you let me have this one, huh?
No, this one's mine.
My man!
Ow.
Did you get it or do it?
Do what?
Act like a human.
On.
Yeah!
What up?
Come on!
I'm serious.
On!
Whoa.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm not gonna give a sweat, I ain't saying nothing, so I just keep my peace, keep my peace.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're not fine, come on.
I just need to lie down somewhere.
Uh-huh, you lie down and you go to sleep.
Sleep is good.
No, not if you have a concussion.
Come on, here, sit down.
Sit.
Hey, hey, we need to talk.
Cameron, I'm a little busy right now.
Can you give me a second?
You know, I...
What?
It's off, okay? The whole thing's off.
What are you talking about?
She never wanted me. She wanted Joey the whole time.
Cameron, do you like the girl?
Yeah.
Yeah, and is she worth all this trouble?
Well, I thought she was, but, you know, I...
Well, she is or she isn't.
See, first of all, Joey is not half the man you are.
Secondly, don't let anyone ever make you feel
I feel like you don't deserve what you want.
Go for it.
Come on.
Why?
This is so patronizing.
Leave it to you to use big words and you're smashed.
I don't think so.
Kate.
Why are you doing this?
I told you, you may have a concussion.
You don't care if I never wake up.
Sure I do.
Why?
Well, then, because then I'd have to start taking out girls who actually like me.
Like you could find one.
Oh, see, that, there.
Who needs affection when I have blind hatred?
I just... Let me sit down for a while.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, jeez!
Whew!
I'm sorry.
So why'd you let him get to you?
Who?
Joey.
I hate him.
Well, you've chosen the perfect revenge,
mainlining tequila.
Well, you know what they say.
Nope, what do they say?
No, no, no, no.
Kat, come on, wake up, look at me.
Listen to me, Kat, open your eyes.
Hey, your eyes have a little green in them.
I don't know if we should go.
Hey, a bunch of us are going to Jared's.
Ready?
I have to be home in 20 minutes.
Well, you know, I don't have to be home till 2, so...
One more chance.
Oh, man, I can't.
Damn! That's a shame.
Well, you wanna go?
Sure.
Chastity? Hey, we passed.
Bitch.
Hey, have fun tonight?
Tons.
Hey, Cameron, um, do you think you could give me a ride home?
I should do this.
Do what?
This.
Start a band?
No, install car stereos.
Yeah, start a band.
My father would love that.
When I ask you to explain
You don't strike me as the type that would ask your father for permission.
Oh, so now you think you know me?
I'm getting there.
The only thing people know about me is that I'm scary.
Yeah, well, I'm the picnic myself.
Uh, so, um, what's up with your dad this year?
Is he patting the ass?
No, he just wants me to be somebody that I'm not.
Who?
Bianca.
Ah, Bianca.
No offense or anything.
I mean, I know everyone digs your sister, but she's without.
You know, you're not as vile as I thought you were.
I'm sorry.
Maybe we should do this another time.
No one has won this war this time.
You never wanted to go sailing with me, did you?
Yes, I did.
No, you didn't.
Well, okay, no, not actually.
Well, then that's all you had to say.
Have you always been this selfish?
Yes.
You know, just because you're beautiful,
that doesn't mean that you can treat people like they don't matter.
I mean, I really liked you, okay?
I defended you when people called you conceited.
I helped you when you asked me to.
I learned French for you, and then you just blow me off so that you could...
And I'm back in the game.
Catch me, lady.
You sway to the rhythm of me eyes.
Dance for me, cowgirl.
Cat, babe, what do we owe you for the table dance?
All right, not that I give a damn,
but how was everybody's weekend?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe we should ask Cat.
Unless she kicked the crap out of your dumb butt,
I don't want to hear about it.
Okay, let's open up our books to page 73,
sign at 141, and listen up.
In faith, I do not love thee with mine eyes,
for they in thee a thousand errors note.
But tis my heart that loves what they despise.
Who in despite of you is pleased to dote?
Now, I know Shakespeare's a dead white guy,
but he knows his shit.
So we can overlook that.
I want you all to write your own version of this sonnet.
Oh, come on.
Yes, miss, I have an opinion about everything.
Do you want this in iambic pentameter?
You're not going to fight me on this?
No, I think it's a really good assignment.
You're just messing with me, aren't you?
No, I'm really looking forward to writing it.
Get out of my class.
What?
Out, get out!
Thanks, Mr. Morgan.
Shut up.
I can't get enough of you, baby.
Yes, it is true.
Hey.
Hey, cool picture.
What's that collar for?
Is that to keep him from licking his stitches?
Kidding.
No, because I know you're a fan.
of Shakespeare?
More than a fan.
We're involved.
Okay.
Who could refrain
that had a heart to love
and in that heart...
Courage to make love known.
It's Macbeth, right?
Right.
So listen.
Now, I have this friend
and he likes your friend.
One more left!
What did you do to her?
I didn't do anything. She would have been too drunk to remember me.
But the plan was working.
What do you care? I thought you wanted out.
Yeah, well, I did, but, uh, that was until she kissed me.
Where?
In the car.
Sorry, Tweed! Sorry!
All right, uh, I talked to her. I got the scoop.
What'd she say?
Hates him with the fire of a thousand suns.
That's a direct quote.
Thanks, Malcolm. That's very comforting of you.
Well, you don't know. She could, uh...
She could need a day to cool off.
Maybe two.
Hey!
Hey! Can you even imagine?
Who the hell would go to that antiquated mating ritual?
I would, but I don't have a date.
Do you really want to get all dressed up so some drakkar noir-wearing Dexter with a boner can feel you up
while you're forced to listen to a band that by definition blows?
All right, all right, we will go. It's not like I've got a dress anyway.
You're looking at this from entirely the wrong perspective. You're making a mistake.
Oh, goody! Something new and different for us.
Hey there, Cupid.
Hi, Joey.
You're concentrating awfully hard considering it's gym class.
Can I help you?
I want to talk to you about prom.
Ow!
Look, you know the deal.
I can't go if Kat doesn't go.
Your sister is going.
Since when?
Oh, let's just say I'm taking care of it.
Here, this should take care of the flowers, the limo,
the tux, everything.
Just make sure she gets to the prom.
You know what, I'm sick of playing your little game.
OK, wait, wait, wait.
You, uh, you sick of, let's say, 300?
I'm not the sort of person who falls in and quickly out of love.
To you I gave my affection right from the start
I have a lover who loves me
How could I break such a heart
Yet still you get my attention
Why do you come here
When you know
I've got troubles enough
Why do you call me
When you know
I can't answer the phone
Make me love
And I don't want to
But make someone else
I'm glad we're not
knowing more
You make me stay
Excuse me, have you seen the feminine mystique?
I've lost my copy.
What are you doing here?
I heard there was a poetry reading.
You're so...
Charming.
Wholesome.
Unwelcome?
You're not as mean as you think you are, you know that?
You're not as badass as you think you are.
Ooh, someone still has her panties in a twist.
Don't for one minute think that you had any effect
whatsoever on my panties.
Then what did I have an effect on?
Other than my upchuck reflex, nothing.
You're right, she's still pissed.
Sweet love, renew thy force.
Hey.
Don't say shit like that to me. People can hear you.
Look, you embarrassed the girl.
Sacrifice yourself on the altar of dignity and even the score.
Listen, don't say shit like that to him.
People can hear you.
There's a new kind of world that's taking over
It's got devils, it's got angels
Sitting on my shoulders
There's a new kind of world that's taking over
You're just too good to be true
Can't take my eyes off of you
You'd be like heaven to touch
I wanna hold you so much
At long last love has arrived
And I thank God I'm alive
You're just too good to be true
Can't take my eyes off of you
I love you, baby
And if it's quite all right
I need you, baby
To warm the lonely night
I love you, baby
Trust in me
when I say, oh, pretty baby, don't bring me down, I pray.
Oh, pretty baby, now that I've found you, stay.
And let me love you, baby.
Let me love you.
Oh!
You look pretty nervous.
Yes, sir.
You're sweating like a pig.
Your eyes are all bloodshot.
Yes, sir.
You've got pot, don't you?
I'm confiscating this.
This, too.
Mr. Chapin, can I talk to you for a second?
What can I do for you, Strafford?
Um, sir, I have some ideas on how we can improve the girls' soccer team.
Great! Let's talk about it later.
The window.
As you know, we have a really big game with Hillcrest High.
Your bicep is huge!
Oh, my God, the other one's even bigger.
You don't take steroids, do you?
Because I've heard that steroids can severely disintegrate your... package.
I mean, not that I'm thinking about your package.
That's not the point.
Let's hope not.
The point is, they kick our butts every year,
and I was thinking I devised a plan
that will enable us to finally defeat them.
Which is?
That thing that you taught us.
What thing?
Misdirection.
I taught you that?
Yeah, you or Siegfried or Roy.
Anyway, that's not important.
Think about it.
They're looking left, and we're running right.
Bang, we score.
We win.
OK, but how do we get them to look left?
Like this.
OK.
Well, now that you've seen the plan,
I'm going to go and show the plan to someone else.
OK.
Thanks.
I can't thank you enough for helping
me sneak out of detention.
Very cool.
No problem.
I thought for sure I was busted when I was
glaring out that window, I tell you.
So how did you keep him distracted?
I dazzled him with my wits.
So what's your excuse?
For?
For acting the way we do.
I don't like to do what people expect.
Why should I live up to other people's expectations
instead of my own?
So you're disappointed from the start,
and then you're covered, right?
Something like that.
Then you screwed up.
How?
You never disappointed me.
Are you up for it?
Up for what?
Oh!
Oh, fuck.
Fascinating thing, you delight me, and I know you're speaking of me.
Fascinating thing, get beside me, I want you to love me.
I'm surprised that you got the edge of the world for you.
That you're lovely, and you're perfect, and that somebody wants you.
I'm surprised that you've never been told before
That you're lovely and you're perfect
And that somebody wants you
I'm surprised that you haven't told before
That you're priceless, yeah, you're holy
When you are not new
Come on, come on, that's the way you're feeling
That's the way you're feeling
All right
No, none of that stuff is true.
State trooper.
Fallacy.
A dead guy in the parking lot.
Rumor.
The duck.
Hearsay.
Bobby Ridge raised balls.
Fact.
But he deserved it, and he tried to grope me in the lunch line.
Fair enough.
The accent.
It's real.
I, uh, lived in Australia until I was 10.
With the pygmies?
Close.
With my mom.
Where were you last year?
I know the porn career is a lie.
Do you?
Tell me something true.
Something true.
I hate peas.
No, something real.
Something no one else knows.
Okay.
You're sweet,
and sexy,
You're completely helpful, man.
You are amazingly self-assured.
Has anyone ever told you that?
I tell myself that every day, actually.
Go to the prom with me.
Is that a request or a command?
Come on, go with me.
No.
No?
Why not?
Because I don't want to.
Because it's a stupid tradition.
Come on, people won't expect you to go.
Why are you pushing this?
What's in it for you?
Oh.
So now I need to have a motive to want to be with you.
You tell me.
You need therapy, you know that? Has anyone ever told you that?
Answer the question, Patrick.
Nothing. There is nothing in it for me. Just the pleasure of your company.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
May I offer you a coin?
Not at all.
Where is my uncle's pen?
I don't know.
Maybe in your drawer.
Let me ask you a question, Cameron.
Cameron.
Comme vous demanderai, tout est sorti avec toi.
Merde.
Oh.
Seven.
Good.
Daddy?
Hi, honey.
Um, I'd like to discuss tomorrow night with you.
Now, as you know, it's the prom.
The prom. Cat has a date?
Well, no.
Don't think you're fooling me for a second.
I know who you want to bend the rules for. It's that hot rod Joey.
What's a hot rod?
It's a...
If your sister's not going, you're not going. End of story.
Okay, let's review.
Cat, not interested. Me, dying to go.
Do you know what happens at proms?
Yes, Daddy, we'll dance, we'll kiss, we'll come home.
It's not quite the crisis situation you imagine.
Kissing, huh?
That's what you think happens?
Got news for you.
Kissing isn't what keeps me up to my elbows
in placenta all day long.
Can we for two seconds ignore the fact
that you're severely unhinged and discuss my need
for a night of teenage normalcy?
What's normal?
Those damn Dawson's River kids sleeping in each other's beds
and whatnot?
Danny, that is so not.
Got news for you.
I'm down.
I've got the 411.
And you are not going out and getting jiggy with some boy
I don't care how dope his ride is.
Ugh!
My mama didn't raise no fool.
Thanks, Bill.
Ridiculous amounts of love across this nation worldwide.
Believe it.
This is the true story.
The real world.
Seattle.
Come in.
Listen, I know...
I know you hate having to sit at home
because I'm not Susie High School.
Like you care.
I do care.
But I'm a firm believer in doing something for your own reasons
and not someone else's.
Well, I wish I had that luxury.
You know, I'm the only sophomore that got asked to go to the prom,
and I can't go because you don't feel like it.
Joey never told you that we went out, did he?
Yeah, okay.
In ninth for a month.
Why?
Because he was, like, such a babe.
But you hate Joey.
Now I do.
So what happened?
Please tell me you're joking.
Just once.
Right after Mom left.
Everyone was doing it, so I did it.
Afterwards, I told him I didn't want to anymore because I wasn't ready.
And he got pissed and he dumped me.
After that, I swore I would never do anything just because everyone else was doing it.
And I haven't since, with the exception of Bogey's party
and my stunning digestive pyrotechnics.
How is it possible that I did not know about this?
I warned him that if he told anyone,
the cheerleading squad would find out how tiny his dick is.
Okay, so why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to let you make up your own mind about him.
Then why did you help Daddy hold me hostage?
It's not like I'm stupid enough to repeat your mistakes.
I guess I thought I was protecting you.
By not letting me experience anything for myself?
Not all experiences are good, Bianca.
You can't always trust the people you want to.
Well, I guess I'll never know, will I?
The gray ceiling on the earth
Well, it's lasted for a while
Take my thoughts for what they're worth
I've been acting like a child
But what else, what else can I do?
I said I'm sorry, yeah, I'm sorry
And ladies with thinning hair or bald spots, GLH solves the problem instantly.
GLH is not a paint or a cover-up.
It's an amazing powder that clings to the tiniest hairs on your head.
It actually builds on itself, leaving you with great, great-looking hair.
And the GLH hair system is not expensive.
Interesting.
Order your GLH hair package now.
Bye, Dad. I'm going to the prom.
Funny, sweetie.
What's that?
A palm dress.
I seem to be hearing that word a lot lately.
Hi.
Wow.
I, um...
Bye, Daddy.
Stop.
Turn.
Explain.
OK.
Remember how you said I could date if Cat dated?
Well, she found this guy who's actually
kind of perfect for her, which is actually
kind of perfect for me because Cameron
asked me to go to the prom.
And I really, really, really want to go.
And since Cat went, I guess I'm allowed to,
based on the aforementioned rule and its previous stipulations,
of course.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go.
I know every cop in town, bucko.
This is not good.
I said I want you to know
I said I want you to know right now
I want you to know
I said I want you to know
Whoa!
Shout!
Hey, hey!
Wow.
You too.
Where'd you get a tux at the last minute?
Oh, just something I had, you know, lying around.
Where'd you get the dress?
Listen, I'm really sorry that I questioned your motives.
I was wrong.
You're forgiven.
Okay.
OK.
Ready for the prom?
Yes, ma'am.
Hi, Mr. Stratford.
I'm Joey.
I'm here to pick up Bianca.
On their minds with their hormones arranging
And they want it all the time
And I know, know what she said
So when I can't just let you go
Have you seen him?
Who?
William!
He asked me to meet him here!
Oh, Mandela, please tell me you haven't progressed to full-on hallucinations.
I love you very much
You're nice to see and nice to touch
But I would never, ever, ever treat you wrong
I've been waiting for you all along
And I know, know that you said so
And I can't just let you go
My lady.
Good sir.
Oh my God!
I called you to favor!
You're my friend, I'm at my wit's end
You say your love is bona fide
But that don't coincide
With the things that you do
When I ask you to be nice
You say you gotta be
Cool to be kind in the right measure
Cool to be kind, it's a very good sign
Cool to be kind means that I love you, baby
You gotta be cool to be kind.
Ooh.
Cool to be kind in the right measure.
Cool to be kind at the very good time.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I know you didn't think you were the only sophomore at the prom.
Joey just picked me up.
Oh, well, congratulations. He's all yours.
Very generous, Princess.
And just so you know, Joey only liked you for one reason.
He even had a bet going with his friends.
He was going to nail you tonight.
Milwaukee!
What?
That's where I was last year.
I wasn't in jail.
I don't know Marilyn Manson, and I didn't sleep in a Spice Girl.
I don't think.
You see, my grandpa, he was ill, so I spent most of the year
on his couch watching Wheel of Fortune and making spaghettios.
End of story.
No way.
Hey, what's Bianca doing here with that cheese dip?
I didn't pay you to take out Kat so that some little punk
could snake me with Bianca.
Nothing in it for you, huh?
The shit hath hitteth the fan.
Yes.
Joey, now a Padre is off.
You messed with the wrong guy.
Now you're gonna pay.
You and that little bitch.
All right, that's enough, okay?
Yeah, you crossed the line.
Oh, come on.
Get up, you little punk.
Oh!
Shit, Bianca.
I'm shooting a nose spray ad tomorrow.
That's for making my date bleed.
That's for my sister.
Oh!
And that's for me.
Ow.
Oh!
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
Are you OK?
Never been better.
Would you give me a chance just to?
You were paid to take me out by the one person I truly hate.
I knew this was a setup.
Kat, it wasn't like that, OK?
Really? What was it like? A down payment now and then a bonus for sleeping with me?
No, I didn't care about the money, okay? I cared...
I cared about you.
You are so not who I thought you were.
I love you.
Hey.
You want?
Thanks.
So you sure you don't want to go sailing with us?
It'll be fun.
No, I'm fine.
Look, I don't know if I ever thanked
you for going last night, but it really meant a lot to me.
I'm glad.
Hey.
You ready?
Bye.
She... she...
I hope so.
Where's your sister going?
She's meeting some bikers.
Big ones. Full of sperm.
Funny.
So tell me about this dance. Was it hopping?
Parts of it.
Which parts?
The part where Bianca beat the hell out of some guy.
Bianca did what?
What's the matter? Upset that I rubbed off on her?
No, impressed.
You know, fathers don't like to admit it
when their daughters are capable of running their own lives.
It means we've become spectators.
Bianca still lets me play a few innings.
You've had me on the bench for years.
When you go to Sarah Lawrence, I won't even be able to watch the game.
When I go?
Oh, boy. Don't tell me you changed your mind.
I would just send him a check.
All right, I assume everyone has found time to complete their poem,
except for Mr. Dunham, who has an excuse.
Chef, close the glasses.
All right, anyone brave enough to read this aloud?
I will.
Lord, here we go.
I hate the way you talk to me and the way you cut your hair.
I hate the way you drive my car.
I hate it when you stare.
I hate your big, dumb combat boots and the way you read my mind.
I hate you so much it makes me sick.
It even makes me rhyme.
I hate it.
I hate the way you're always right.
I hate it when you lie.
I hate it when you make me laugh, even worse
when you make me cry.
I hate it when you're not around and the fact
that you didn't call.
But mostly, I hate the way I don't hate you.
Not even close.
Not even a little bit.
Not even at all.
Nice, huh?
A Fender Strat?
Is it for me?
Yeah, I thought you could use it, you know, when you start your band.
Besides, I had some extra cash, you know.
Some asshole paid me to take out this really great girl.
Is that right?
Yeah, but I screwed up, I am.
I fell for him.
Really?
It's not every day you find a girl who'll flash someone to get you out of detention.
Oh, God.
You can't just buy me a guitar every time you screw up, you know.
Yeah, I know.
But then you know there's always drums and bass and maybe even one day a tambourine.
And don't you see you can...
to baby
I want you to want me.
I need you to need me.
I'd love you to love me.
I'm begging you to beg me.
Shine a whole bunch of news.
Put on a brand new shirt.
I'll get on earth and work.
If you say that you love me
Did I, did I, did I see you crying?
Oh, did I, did I, did I see you crying?
Feeling all alone without a friend
You know you'll be like dying
Oh, did I, did I, did I see you crying?
Crying
Feeling all alone with that friend
You know you'll feel like dying
Oh, did not, did not, did not see you crying
I want you to want me
I need you to need me
I'd love you to love me
I'm begging you to beg me
I want you to want me
No offense.
I know everyone digs your sister and all, but she's without.
You know, you're not as vile as I thought you were.
Eww!
Okay.
Let's go!
You're just messing with me, aren't you?
No, I'm really looking forward to doing it.
Go see Miss Perky.
What?
Go, Perkys! Go, now.
Once again, Perky now is the second one.
Perkys, now, Perkys, now!
Right away, right away.
Now, Perkys!
Hey, hey, hey.
Now, Perkys, Perkys, now.
He's now.
Who gave you the shot?
Herc.
Oh.
Bianca, let's go.
We're all congregating around Mr. Cuervo.
Um, I'll see you around, okay?
Don't worry.
There's better for you.
And it's right here.
Come here.
No, I wanted you for so long.
You messed with the wrong guy.
Now you're gonna pay.
You and that little bitch.
All right, that's enough, okay?
You crossed the line.
What, are you kidding me?
I'm driving so I get to pick the tunes.
And it's my car.
Oh!
I want some coffee!
Could I get a prophylactic?
A prophylactic?
Ah.
Let go!
Why would you set me up like that?
Oh, God, I just wanted...
To completely damage me, to send me to therapy forever?
No, I just wanted...
Oh! Oh!
Shall we go to my office?
Tootsweet!
Oh, my God!
Thank you.